[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do  the male name Thomas and its derivatives Tom, Thom, Tomas, Tomm all mean?", "correct_answer": "Twin", "incorrect_answers": ["Brave", "Doubt", "Soldier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the actress starring in And Your Mother Too (Y Tu Mama Tambien)?", "correct_answer": "Maribel Verdu", "incorrect_answers": ["Lumi Cavazos", "Catalina Sandino Moreno", "Penelope Cruz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2007, where was a new record for the biggest country flag set?", "correct_answer": "Israel", "incorrect_answers": ["North Korea", "Venezuela", "Mexico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the first Popeyes restaurant opened?", "correct_answer": "1972", "incorrect_answers": ["1973", "1971", "1970"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1856 the US Army formed the U.S. Army Camel Corps.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the title of a 1903 clasic tune:  Shine on...", "correct_answer": "...Harvest Moon", "incorrect_answers": ["...Chrome Fenders", "...You Crazy Diamond", "...In  The Sunshine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did H. Taylor Howard invent in 1976?", "correct_answer": "Satellite dish", "incorrect_answers": ["The QWERTYU keyboard", "Windows XP", "The cell phone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie won 8 Academy Awards out of 10 nominations at the 81st Academy Awards 2009?", "correct_answer": "Slumdog Millionaire", "incorrect_answers": ["Milk", "The Dark Knight", "The Curious Case of Benjamin Button"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is the longest river in the world", "correct_answer": "The Nile", "incorrect_answers": ["Themes", "The Amazon", "Danube"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of my companion animals entered the bathroom and brought about my ailurophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Cats", "incorrect_answers": ["Ferrets", "Birds", "Dogs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the word Triceratops mean?", "correct_answer": "Three Horned Face", "incorrect_answers": ["Three Big Horns", "Big Horned Beast", "Three Horned Head"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Greek word hamartia, used in Aristotles Poetics, means what?", "correct_answer": "A fatal flaw", "incorrect_answers": ["Incredible strength", "Drama", "A broken heart"]}]